Class 1-1.
一年一班
They were in the midst of an unprecedented crisis.
這個班級正面臨前所未有的危機
The atmosphere was tense, on the verge of collapse.
瀰漫著瀕臨瓦解的氛圍
Komi! Komi!
古見同學！
Curses flew through the air.
叫罵聲此起彼落
HUH?
啊？
The delinquents from episode three appeared.
曾在第三集登場的 神秘不良少年再度現身
The class is now…
這個班級現在…
That's why I think Komi should…!
所以我認為古見同學應該…
I'm Komi's…!
我想看古見同學的…
-I want Komi to…! -Komi! Komi!
-我要讓古見同學… -古見同學！
Um, ah, hey everyone.
大家不要這樣
…deciding what to do for the culture festival.
正在表決在文化祭班上要做些什麼
Alright.
好
Okay, I got it!
好，我知道了！
Just stop!
大家不要吵了！
We voted and amazingly, it was a tie.
我們投票表決 結果每項提案票數都一樣
Let's all hear one last pitch for each choice,
所以請各位再各自用一句話 來宣揚自己的提案
and vote one more time!
然後重新再表決一次！
And for better or worse,
無論表決結果是好是壞
that'll be our choice!
那就是最後的定案！
That's what you want to say, right Tadano?
只野同學，你是想這麼說吧？
Huh? Uh… Alright, let's do that.
什麼？好，那就這樣
NAJIMI'S PROPOSAL
（長名馴染的主張）
Above all, I think we should do a maid cafe.
反正我一定要推薦女僕咖啡廳啦
It may be overdone and old. But listen.
雖然很常見 可能也有人會覺得落伍，可是啊
You want to see it, don't you? Komi in a maid outfit.
你們不會很想看看 古見同學的女僕裝扮嗎？
Of course we do!
當然很想看！
Me next.
輪到我了
-YAMAI'S PROPOSAL -I propose a haunted house.
-（山井戀的主張） -我要推薦的是鬼屋
It is a lot of work and money.
雖然很花時間，也很花錢
But that's just the kind of thing that would bring us together, right?
但這樣才能培養大家的感情不是嗎？
And in a darkened room,
況且在黑暗的地方
we could get away with touching Komi's butt.
感覺還可以偷摸古見同學的屁股呢
You have a point!
有道理！
That's not okay!
當然不可以
-NAKANAKA'S PROPOSAL -I think we should make a band.
-（中中思春的主張） -我覺得組樂團演唱比較好
I know not many people would be featured,
雖然能上台當主角的同學不多
but some don't want to be in the spotlight.
有些人會無法沐浴在聚光燈下
Anyway…
可是…
Don't you want to hear the voice of our god?
你們難道不想聽聽神的歌聲嗎？
Huh? We want to hear it!
什麼？好想聽！
-AGARI'S PROPOSAL -I think we should do a whack-a-mole game!
-（上理卑美子的主張） -我覺得打地鼠遊戲比較好！
Ow!
好疼！
I want to be whacked by Komi.
我想讓古見同學打我
-She's a genius?! -CLASS MASOCHISTS
-是天才？ -（班上的受虐狂）
-SHINOBINO'S PROPOSAL -How about making an indie film?
-（忍野裳乃的主張） -辦自製電影放映會如何？
Rescuing Princess Komi, snatched by ninjas.
電影內容是忍者 去營救被擄走的古見公主
-THE KOMI BODYGUARDS -Wait. It's gotta be a medieval story.
-（古見親衛隊的隊員） -慢著，應該拍成西洋騎士故事吧
Ninjas are nonsense!
忍者的主題太莫名其妙了！
We don't have the budget.
預算上有困難
-ONEMINE'S PROPOSAL -I think we should sell rice balls.
-（尾根峰寧寧的主張） -我建議開個飯糰店
Everyone needs a snack, right?
大家總得吃點輕食吧？
And I'm good at making rice balls.
而且我很會捏飯糰呢
-A rice ball made by our god! -Huh?
-古見同學捏的飯糰！ -什麼？
A rice ball made by Komi!
古見同學親手捏的飯糰！
YADANO'S PROPOSAL
（矢田野真華留的主張）
Bowling, billiards, darts.
保齡球、撞球、擲飛鏢
Anything to do with competition.
只要是能比輸贏的，什麼都好
-MAKERU FAN CLUB -Wow Makeru, you're so cool!
-（真華留粉絲團的人） -真華留好帥喔！
Makeru has a fan club?
真華留粉絲團？
-ONIGASHIMA'S PROPOSAL -Let's do fortune telling!
-（鬼島朱子的主張） -來擺占卜攤吧
Check your compatibility with Komi.
可以占卜看看 和古見同學的相配度呢
Yeah! I want to know my compatibility!
天啊，好想知道喔！
-NON-OTAKU YUJI OTAKU'S PROPOSAL -We should sell fan fiction.
-（小宅優治的主張） -我想推薦同人誌即賣會
If Komi dresses up in cosplay everyone will buy them.
由古見同學以角色扮演的裝扮 賣本子肯定會賣得超好
A new character?
新角色嗎？
-YAMAI'S 2ND PROPOSAL -We should sell frankfurters too!
-（山井戀的主張2） -我也想賣法蘭克福腸！
I can get Komi to su--
我想讓古見同學把我的法蘭克福腸…
I won't let you say it!
不准再說了！
NOKOKO INAKA'S PROPOSAL
（井中乃來子的主張）
A disco!
迪斯可舞廳！
Say it out loud.
妳要說出來啊
CREPE STAND, DISCO, FILM, BAND, MAID CAFE: 3 VOTES
（賣可麗餅、迪斯可、電影 樂團、女僕咖啡廳：3票）
It was a tie.
全部同票
-KOMI! KOMI! -I WANT KOMI TO…
-古見同學！ -我要古見同學…
Will history will repeat itself again?
歷史又要重演了嗎？
Oh, by the way.
啊，能順便問一下嗎？
What did you vote for?
古見同學剛才投了哪一個？
KOMI! KOMI!
古見同學！
I mean, only if you're comfortable telling me.
如果願意再跟我說就行
I CHOSE THE MAID CAFE.
（我投女僕咖啡廳）
Huh? Oh!
什麼？是喔！
The maid cafe?
妳投了女僕咖啡廳嗎？
THAT'S SURPRISING…
（滿意外的）
MAID CAFE: 36 VOTES
（女僕咖啡廳：36票）
Maid cafe it is!
就決定是女僕咖啡廳！
The class was united.
全班團結一致
Help over here!
這邊需要幫忙！
MISSION 37 "IT'S JUST FESTIVAL PREPARATIONS."
（任務37 準備文化祭）
I'll be done soon.
我這裡馬上就好
Someone take out the garbage.
垃圾幫忙丟一下
I have to carry this. Move the desks!
我要搬東西進去，把桌子移開
KOMI WANTS TO HELP BUT CAN'T.
（古見同學很想幫忙卻幫不上忙）
Hey, someone hold that end!
喂，來人幫我舉另一邊！
OKAY!
（好）
Anyone!
來幫幫忙！
It's okay. I'll do it.
不用啦，我來就好
Komi, you can
古見同學去那邊吧
rest on that throne!
到神座休息吧！
I don't have enough supplies at all.
我們材料完全不夠耶
Culture Festival Committee Member!
文化祭執行委員！
Hm?
什麼？
-Yes? What is it? -OTORI IS A SPACE CADET.
-是，有什麼事嗎？ -（尾雞同學個性溫吞）
We don't have enough supplies so I want someone to go buy more.
材料不夠用，希望有人幫忙出去買
I see.
這樣啊
SLIP!
（絆倒）
I mean, could you choose someone and tell them to go?
所以妳可以派個人去買嗎？
Work out a budget and all that.
也需要討論預算
I see.
這樣啊
Is she okay?
沒問題嗎？
Alright, I'll go buy them.
那我出去買吧
You will?
妳要自己去嗎？
Don't you think a couple more people should go along?
要不要再多帶一、兩個人去啊？
I suppose.
說得也是
Alright.
那麼…
Komi, do you want to come with me?
古見同學，我們一起去吧！
Huh?
什麼？
Is it alright to ask Komi?
可以找古見同學做事嗎？
She's a god! It's sacrilegious!
她可是神耶，太荒謬了！
You seem free. Let's go!
我看妳好像沒事做，我們一起去吧
NOD
（點頭）
This worries me…
感覺好不安
-I'm worried. I'll go too! -ONEMINE IS LIKE A BIG SISTER.
-只有兩個人會不安吧，我也一起去 -（尾根峰同學是大姐姐）
Onemine! Good save!
尾根峰同學，幹得好！
I want to go too!
我也想一起去！
-Me too!
-我也是！ -我也要！
We can't!
不行
We have to make this culture festival a success for Komi's sake…
為了古見同學，我們的使命是 必須成功辦好這次的文化祭
There's no time for shopping.
沒有時間去買東西
I guess we should stay.
還是算了
Alright, I'll--
那我去…
If we can't go, you can't either!
你休想去！
Whoa.
哇
IN THE END, THREE OF THEM WENT.
（結果是三個人一起去）
When a person has extreme social anxiety,
所謂的“交流障礙症” 是指不擅長和人交流的一種症狀
they struggle to communicate with others.
或是指有這種症狀的人
Bear in mind, they only struggle to form connections.
不過需要注意的是 這些人只是不擅長社交
It doesn't mean that they don't want to.
但並不表示他們不想和別人有往來
We're here!
我們到了！
It sure took a while.
雖然花了不少時間
Now, what do we need?
話說要買什麼啊？
Panels, paint, cloth…
板子、油漆、布和…
Alright! Let's split up…
好，那我們分頭去買…
No, let's go together.
算了，還是一起去吧
Onemine felt like something bad might happen if she left them alone.
尾根峰同學覺得 如果和這兩人分開會有危險
Home improvement stores are so exciting!
居家修繕量販店這種地方 會讓人感到興奮呢！
You know what I mean?
妳懂嗎？
Is this the kind of panel they need?
板子買這個就行了嗎？
Kaede?
小楓
Yeah, I think I know what you mean.
我也有點懂妳說的
Huh?
什麼？
It's my first time here, though.
雖然我是第一次來
Oh! You mean about home improvement stores being exciting.
我懂了！是剛才說的 居家修繕量販店會讓人興奮？
Is that right.
這樣啊
It's your first time at a…
原來小楓沒來過…
-GONE -She disappeared!
-（突然消失） -人不見了！
Th-This is an emergency! Let's split up and look for her!
事態緊急，趕快分頭去找！
Huh?
真奇怪
I wonder where everyone went?
-（除了工作人員以外禁止進入） -大家都跑去哪裡了？
Oh, Komi. Hi there.
哎呀，這不是古見同學嗎？妳好啊
I'm sorry for causing trouble.
不好意思給妳添麻煩了
Are you mad?
妳在生氣嗎？
Oh, then I'm glad.
那真是太好了
You seem like…
妳是不是…
you want to chat.
想說什麼呢？
Take your time.
慢慢說沒關係
You're going to write it?
妳要用寫的啊？
WHY DID YOU ASK ME TO COME?
（妳為什麼會找我一起來呢？）
Hm. Good question.
這個嘛，是為什麼呢？
I don't know.
我也不知道耶
It's just…
或許是…
when I saw you with Tadano and the others,
看到妳和只野同學他們在一起
I wanted to become friends with you too, I guess.
讓我也很想和妳做朋友
Hm?
什麼？
IN JUNIOR HIGH, DURING CLASS EVENTS,
（國中的時候，班上的活動）
I COULDN'T REALLY HELP OR PARTICIPATE.
（我幾乎都幫不上忙 所以我都很少參加）
I FELT BAD I COULDN'T HELP.
（無法幫忙，讓我很歉疚）
WHEN YOU ASKED ME TO HELP…
（所以今天妳找我幫忙）
I WAS REALLY HAPPY.
（我好開心）
GONE
（突然消失）
Komi!
古見同學！
-What's this? -Miss!
-這是什麼呀？ -這位客人！
Sheesh! Kaede, you're such a handful.
真是的，小楓 妳不要給我們添麻煩好嗎？
Onemine.
尾根峰同學
I'm friends with Komi now!
我和古見同學成為朋友了呢
Really? That's nice.
是喔，那很好啊
Oh, of course, you're my friend too.
啊，妳當然也是我的朋友喔
Yeah, thanks.
這樣啊，謝謝妳啦
Komi!
古見同學！
Let's work hard for the culture festival!
我們一起努力，辦好文化祭吧！
Yes.
好
She spoke!
居然說話了！
We have to ask her to help out more!
看來我得多找她幫忙才行！
The shopping team is back!
採購組回來了！
Let's go help them carry the supplies!
我們去幫她們拿東西吧！
Yeah.
說得也是
We're going to hand out festival flyers!
現在要去發文化祭的傳單！
Here we are! At Itan Shopping Street by the school.
發傳單的地點就是這裡 學校附近的伊旦商店街
We'll give flyers to the shopkeepers, and ask them to put them up!
我們要發傳單給這裡的商家 請他們把傳單貼在店裡！
C'mon Komi, you're up!
那麼古見同學，妳來發！
I figured that was your plan!
我就知道他打算這樣做！
Okay, first you show her how it's done.
那你先示範一次看看啊
Well, if you insist.
什麼啊？真拿你們沒辦法
Hello sir! Will you put up our flyer?
你好，叔叔，可以幫我們貼傳單嗎？
That was fast!
未免也太快了吧！
Still talking?
而且還聊起來了
He'll put up the flyer!
老闆說可以讓我們貼！
And I got some croquettes!
還送我們可樂餅！
The very embodiment of people skills!
社交能力怎麼會這麼強啊！
-I FEEL LIKE I CAN DO IT. -Really?
-（我覺得我好像也能辦到） -真的嗎？
Alright Komi, let's do this!
那麼古見同學，妳去試試看吧！
Welcome!
歡迎光臨！
Go ahead, that seat's free.
請進，有位子喔
What would you like?
要點什麼呢？
KOMI SAT DOWN.
（古見同學坐了下來）
-KOMI ATE A WHOLE MEAL. -Huh?
-（結果古見同學吃個飯就出來了） -什麼？
Okay, let's try a place you've been to before.
啊，不然去妳去過的店吧
Shoko!
硝子！
And your friends?
他們是妳朋友嗎？
Sniff, sniff.
我聞一下
Alright.
我瞭解了
You want me to put up the flyer here, right?
只要把這傳單貼在店裡就行了吧？
That's my brilliant boss!
不愧是非凡美髮師！
RAMEN DARO
（拉麵大郎）
They're kindred spirits.
交流障礙症的兩人間的心電感應
We still have one left.
還剩一張呢
Let's give it to the person at this house!
好，就發給這一家吧！
How can you be so assertive?
你為什麼可以如此毫不猶豫啊？
Hello? Who's there?
來了，哪一位啊？
Oh, I'm sorry. Did we wake him up?
對不起，我們吵醒寶寶了嗎？
It's alright. He's always like this.
別擔心，他每次都這樣
We're students from Itan High School.
我們是伊旦高中的學生
We're having a culture festival next week.
下禮拜學校要舉辦文化祭
You're welcome to come.
歡迎來玩喔
Oh! Thank you.
這樣啊，謝謝你們
RUMBLE
（隆隆聲）
Huh? He stopped crying.
什麼？寶寶不哭了
Ah! Kokko!
啊，古古！
-Kokko! -Hm? What is it?
-古古！ -怎麼了？
Ah.
啊
We're finished!
通通發完了！
Good job Tadano and Komi and me!
只野同學、古見同學，還有我 大家都辛苦了！
Let's head back.
那我們回去吧
Kokko!
古古！
We have more work to do, Kokko.
得回去繼續準備呢，古古同學
The night before the festival.
文化祭前夕
Many of the students stayed behind,
許多學生都留在學校
preparing for the following day.
為隔天的活動進行準備
But the scene…
然而他們的模樣…
was one of corpses.
就像一堆屍體
It was like a room full of dead bodies.
教室中呈現的是一片死屍累累的慘狀
Hey!
快起來！
We made rice balls!
我們做了飯糰！
Whoa!
喔！
The corpses came back to life.
屍體復活了
Wow!
哇！
-Hang on. -These rice balls…
-等等 -這些飯糰裡…
Some were made by Komi!
也有古見同學親手做的！
Which ones? Which did she make?
哪一個？到底是哪一個飯糰？
I can't choose!
不可輕易出手！
Who, who made the rice balls…
哪個飯糰是哪個人做的啊？
-NAJIMI'S TESTIMONY -I made strangely-shaped ones.
-（馴染的證詞） -我做了奇形怪狀的飯糰喔
Cubes and diamonds and so on.
譬如方形的，還有菱形的
-ONEMINE'S TESTIMONY -Mine are a little big.
-（尾根峰同學的證詞） -我做的可能大了一些
But they're not too big to eat!
不過那大小還是能吃啦
KOMI'S TESTIMONY
（古見同學的證詞）
Komi, yours were a nice shape.
我記得妳做的形狀很漂亮
-YAMAI'S TESTIMONY -Komi made small rice balls!
-（山井同學的證詞） -古見同學做的飯糰很小！
They weren't nicely shaped!
一點都不漂亮喔！
-So give me all the nice ones! -SOMEONE IS LYING! GUESS WHO?
-所以漂亮的飯糰通通給我吧！ -（有一人說謊，大家猜猜看！）
Rock, scissors, paper…
剪刀、石頭、布…
-I'll never eat this. -Hey! Let me go!
-這飯糰我要珍藏一生 -不要攔著我！
I'll offer it to the deities.
我要把它放在神壇
Precious…
好尊貴
I guess this is Najimi's.
我這個應該是馴染做的吧
It's a very well-made cube.
不過這四方型捏得還真是漂亮
How was this made?
到底是怎麼捏出來的？
Nom.
啊姆
Mm?
嗯？
It's good!
喔，好吃耶！
Now,
大家猜猜
whose rice ball is Tadano eating, I wonder?
只野同學是吃到了誰捏的飯糰呢？
KOMI COPIED NAJIMI AND ATTEMPTED ONE STRANGELY-SHAPED RICE BALL.
（古見同學模仿馴染 也做了一個奇形怪狀的飯糰）
NICE CUBE, KOMI!
（妳捏的四方形好漂亮）
Hi everyone!
歡迎大家！
Welcome to the 23rd Itan High School Culture Festival!
歡迎來到第23屆伊旦高中文化祭！
1-1 MAID CAFE ITAN
（一年一班，伊旦女僕咖啡廳）
What's wrong, Komi?
怎麼了？古見同學
Oh, you wanted a longer one?
喔，妳想穿長裙款啊？
A-ha-ha, there are none.
哈哈，沒有喔
-Yamai fell! -She passed out!
-山井同學倒下去了！ -她昏倒了！
-Yamai's faking! -Kidding! We made a longer one for you.
-山井同學根本沒昏倒！ -騙妳的啦，有為了妳做長裙款啦
-Yamai's shooting a low-angle video! -They're so loud.
-她從低角度偷錄影！ -真是有夠吵
MAID EXPERT: TATSUHITO AKIDO
（女僕專家：明戶達人）
TATSUHITO AKIDO (32)
（女僕專家 明戶達人，32歲）
The maid expert's morning starts early.
女僕專家早上起得很早
It's 6 a.m. He decides which maid cafe to visit.
早上6點決定當天 要去哪家女僕咖啡廳
One per day.
一天去一間
On that day,
在那一天
He thinks only of that maid cafe.
都要想著那家女僕咖啡廳
As soon as he decides, he cleanses his body.
決定了之後，沐浴淨身
"I mustn't make a bad impression on the maids."
“絕不能讓女僕們有不愉快的感覺”
That's Akido's motto.
這是明戶的口頭禪
Here's where Akido chose today.
明戶今天選的是這間
Itan High School Culture Festival Class 1-1 Event, Maid Cafe.
伊旦高中文化祭 一年一班的女僕咖啡廳
Though it's only a high school culture festival,
雖然充其量只是高中文化祭
if it's too sub-par, I'll just make an excuse and…
但如果太不像樣，我也會抱怨一句…
Welcome back, Master!
您回來了啊，主人！
Oh, uh, thank you.
啊，謝謝
Akido is a regular otaku
明戶是個普通的宅男
so he shrinks in front of a real girl.
所以在真實世界的 女生面前就會龜縮起來
Oh-ho. Excellent attention to detail for a high school festival.
喔，就文化祭來說，還滿講究的嘛
But inside his head, he's high and mighty.
可是在腦海裡態度卻是高高在上
Thank you for waiting!
久等了！
Can I get you something to eat?
請問有什麼想吃的東西嗎？
Uh, I'll have the Omurice Served with Lov--
啊，那就這個“女僕的愛心蛋包飯”
Yessir!
遵命！
Ah.
喔
The peppy character… Very nice.
是活潑型角色啊，很不錯
What is thine desire?
你必須選擇你渴望的餐點
Wh-Whoa! I-I'm sorry!
啊呀，對不起！
Ugh. Hurry up and decide.
唉，快點決定好嗎？
Uh…
什麼？
Geeky, clumsy, prickly, peppy.
中二型、笨拙型、傲嬌型、活潑型
They've got all the archetypes.
女僕的類型還滿多樣的嘛
Oh!
喔！
Uh.
呃
Um.
啊
Wha…?!
這…
W-Why is she scowling at me like that?
她為什麼要這樣瞪我？
Oh! I know.
啊，我懂了！
I've been ogling the maids so openly.
因為我一直盯著女僕看
It's certainly not appropriate for a man to have feelings for his maids.
對女僕抱有不當遐想 的確不是一個好主人該有的行為
That's why you're mad, right?
所以妳才會這麼生氣嗎？
Ah.
啊
Pa…
對…
on…
了…
Pa…on…?
“對了”？
"Patronizing"! I knew it!
她想說“答對了”？ 我猜得果然沒錯！
*PARDON ME
（對不起了）
Here's your omurice!
久等了，這是您的蛋包飯！
I… I'll be going.
我要走了
GLOOM
（沮喪）
KOMI THINKS HE'S UPSET BECAUSE OF HER POOR SERVICE.
（古見同學以為客人悶悶不樂 是因為自己服務不周）
Please…
請再…
Uh…
呃…
C'mon Komi, the farewell greeting is,
古見同學，妳這樣不行喔 送客時應該要說
"Please come back soon, Master!"
“主人，請您慢走！”
Right?
對吧？
Saying the wrong farewell greeting is taboo for a maid.
連送客的用詞都會說錯 這女僕不合格啊
But…
可是…
I guess she's an ice-queen type.
這算是酷嬌型嗎？
Hm?
嗯？
Maid expert, Tatsuhito Akido.
女僕專家，明戶達人
Once again, this encounter will take him to a new place.
這次的邂逅應該會 帶他前往下一個新天地吧
MAID CAFE
（女僕咖啡廳）
Tadano! Tadano!
只野同學！
We have the maid outfit that Komi rejected!
古見同學剛才脫下來的女僕裝 多出來了，沒人穿喔！
No.
我才不穿
Woo-woo!
好期待！
I said no.
我都說我不要了
MAIDS CHANGING
（女僕換裝中）
TADANO
（只野同學）
-What are you doing, Tadano? -It looks stupid, Tadano.
-你搞什麼啊？只野 -你穿起來一點都不適合
-Not bad. -Cut it out, guys!
-其實還不錯 -各位，拜託不要這樣！
STARE
（緊盯）
Can I take it off yet?
我可以脫下來了嗎？
You chose this, so take it seriously.
只野同學，既然要做就要認真做
You made me wear it!
是你逼我穿的好嗎？
Shoko! I've arrived!
硝子，我來看妳了！
Komi's mom is here!
古見同學的媽媽來了！
Right this way!
請上座！
Thanks!
謝謝啊！
H-Here's some water.
請喝開水
Huh?
什麼？
Tadano?
你是只野同學嗎？
Uh, yes.
啊，是的
Oh. I see…
啊，這樣啊
It… It's not like that, okay?
不是伯母想得那樣
What are you doing? Shosuke, come here!
你在那裡做什麼？笑介也過來呀！
-Sho… -…suke?
-“笑…” -“介”？
Wow! So cool and cute!
天啊，又帥又可愛！
ALL THE MAIDS STOLE HIM AWAY.
（全體女僕都聚到他這裡）
SHOSUKE FELT UNCOMFORTABLE AND LEFT IMMEDIATELY.
（笑介弟弟感覺不自在 馬上就離開了）
Hitohito! I was bored, so I came.
哥哥，我閒著沒事就來了
Oh.
啊
Uh.
呃
Don't act like that.
妳不要嚇到好嗎？
Hey, Mom? Did you see?
媽媽，妳看到了嗎？
Yeah, you were right about him.
對，哥哥果然是那個傾向
Right about what?!
是指哪個傾向？
MAIDS ON BREAK
（女僕休息中）
Darn you Najimi.
可惡，都怪馴染那小子
Hm?
什麼？
Komi! Good work out there!
古見同學，辛苦妳了！
Today went really well!
生意興隆，真是太好了！
This doesn't suit me, does it?
這件衣服不適合我對吧？
YOU LOOK CUTE.
（很可愛）
Huh? Oh, thank you… very much.
是嗎？謝謝妳
The two started to feel awkward.
不知為何，兩人都有點難為情
ITAN FESTIVAL (AKA KOMI FES)
（伊旦祭 又稱古見祭）
To be continued!
下集待續！
Subtitle translation by: Claire Tanaka
字幕翻譯：馬慈光